http://www.conestogac.on.ca/terms/

FACULTY & STAFF PORTAL
Information For:
Athletics
Co-Curricular Record (CCR)
Athletics
Co-Curricular Record (CCR)
FACULTY & STAFF PORTAL
Information for:
Website privacy, terms of use and conditions
Conestoga College Institute of Technology and Advanced Learning (the "College") operates and maintains this website,
www.conestogac.on.ca (the "Site") including all content thereon. By accessing, browsing or using the Site, you accept and agree to these terms and conditions (the "Terms").Terms of useYou shall not, without our prior written permission, use the Site for purposes other than your own personal, non-commercial use. Further, you may not frame the Site or any part thereof on any Internet website. You acquire absolutely no right or licenses to the Site other than the limited right to use the Site in accordance with the Terms. You shall not use the Site for any purposes except as expressly provided herein.These Terms of Use apply to all visitors to and users of the Site, including any mobile version. By accessing or using the Site, you signify that you have read, understand and agree to be bound by these Terms of Use. You also agree to be bound by these Terms of Use if you post www.conestogac.on.ca links on your site.Information provided for convenienceThe information on this website is provided as a convenience and is not the official source of information about College programs and services. Individuals should refer to approved College policies and other similar documents to support their decision-making. We cannot and do not represent or warrant that all the information contained in this website is accurate.Google Translate disclaimerThe Conestoga College website and its web pages are intended to be read in English. Any translation of the website and its web pages may be imprecise and inaccurate in whole or in part. The translation we suggest is Google Translate. Please note that this website provides "machine translation" and is provided as a convenience. You should use an experienced human English translator to provide you with a more precise and accurate translation into your native language. You access and use any translation at your own risk.You assume all risk, liability, and responsibility for any translation. While reasonable efforts are made to provide a translation, no liability and no responsibility are assumed by Conestoga College or Google for any errors, omissions, or ambiguities in the translations or other information provided by the free translation of this website. In no event is either Conestoga, its affiliates and associated parties, liable for any loss or damages whatsoever arising out of your use of the free translation of the website or the content thereof, including direct, indirect, incidental, consequential or punitive damages.External linksLinks to other websites are provided as a resource. Conestoga College accepts no responsibility for the content of linked sites. These links are provided solely as a convenience to you. Conestoga College does not endorse the information contained therein or guarantee its quality, accuracy, reliability, completeness, currency, timeliness, non-infringement, merchantability or fitness for any purpose.User content posted on the siteYou are solely responsible for the photos, profiles (including your name, image and likeness), forum messages and comments, notes, text, information, music, video, listings and other content that you upload, publish or display on the Site, or transmit to or share with other users. You may not post, transmit or share user content on the Site that you did not create or that you do not have permission to post.The College reserves the right to review the Site and may edit, delete or remove (without notice) any content or user content in our sole discretion, at any time and for any reason, including content that in our sole judgement violates these Terms of Use or our Privacy Policy, or which might be offensive, illegal, or that might violate the rights, harm or threaten the safety of others.By posting user content to any part of the Site, you automatically grant, and you represent and warrant that you have the right to grant, to the College an irrevocable, perpetual, non-exclusive, transferable, fully paid, worldwide license (with the right to sublicense) to use, copy, publicly perform, publicly display, reformat, translate, excerpt (in whole or part) and distribute such user content for any purpose. You waive any and all claims you may now or later have in any jurisdiction to "moral rights" or equivalent rights of authorship with respect to the content. You may remove your user content from the Site at any time. If you choose to remove your user content, the license granted above will automatically expire; however you acknowledge that we may retain archived copies of your user content.Web server logs and cookiesThe College uses standard web server log files to collect site visitation statistics. Web server logging does collect machine-specific information such as IP address, operating system and web browser type. Logs may also provide information about user pathways through the website. The College collects this information in order to understand how its website is used and to plan for future enhancements to the website.The College website uses cookies to support site visitation statistics and functions such as forms processing. Visitors to our website may reject any or all of our cookies through their web browser preferences. Site visitors should be aware that certain features of the Conestoga College website, such as forms and surveys, may require the use of cookies to function properly.TrademarksConestoga College, and all other names, logos, seals or other symbols that are representative of the College are trademarks of Conestoga College. Use, reproduction, copying or redistribution of trademarks without the written permission of Conestoga College is prohibited.Disclaimer and limitation of liabilityConestoga College, its Board of Governors, officers, employees and agents are not liable to you for any damages, harm or injury whatsoever including without limitation direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequential or punitive damages, lost profits, damages resulting from lost data or business interruption, arising from or relating to the use of or inability to use the Site, whether based on warranty, contract, tort other legal theory, regardless of whether any of Conestoga, its Board of Governors, officers, employees or agents has been negligent or has been advised of the possibility of such damages.Important information about college programs and servicesIn reading information on this website, individuals should be aware of the following:Programs and courses promoted on this website may or may not be offered depending upon the number of students who enrol and other operational reasons.The College may change, without notice, the offering of and the content of any program or course, the applicable fees, and any rule, regulation or standard pertaining to admission, advancement or graduation.Individuals should not rely on Conestoga College for any information about the qualifications, requirements and costs for external accreditations, designations, certifications and recognitions and should rely exclusively on information provided directly from the applicable external organization.The College provides no warranty or guarantee of any kind that any of the College’s courses will be accepted by any other institution for credit or advanced standing at any time, regardless of the standing that any such course is currently given or is expected to be given in the future.Any information provided by the College in respect of future education, employment or income prospects of students should be understood as a statement of the College’s objectives. These objectives may not be met and may be subject to change. The College does not guarantee any future education, employment or income prospects of students, and will not be liable for any loss, damage or inconvenience suffered or incurred by any student, prospective student or third party as a result of reliance on the aforesaid information provided by the College.IndemnityYou agree to indemnify and hold Conestoga College, its subsidiaries and affiliates and each of their directors, officers, contractors, partners and employees, harmless from and against any loss, liability, claim, demand, damages, costs and expenses arising out of or in direct connection with any user content you post or share on or through the Site, your use of the Site, your conduct in connection with the Site or with other users of the Site, or any violation of the Agreement or of any law or the rights of any third party.Governing lawThe Terms are governed by the laws of the Province of Ontario and the federal laws of Canada applicable therein, and these laws apply to the use of the Site, notwithstanding your domicile, residency or physical location. You hereby attorn to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of the Province of Ontario and all courts competent to hear appeals therefrom. The Site is intended for use only in jurisdictions where it may lawfully be offered for use.ConditionsWe reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add or delete portions of these Terms of Use at any time. Your continued use of the service or the Site after any such changes are posted constitutes your acceptance of the new Terms of Use. It is your responsibility to regularly check this page to determine if there have been changes to these Terms of Use and to review such changes.Privacy noticeConestoga College collects personal information from students under the legal authority of the
Ontario Colleges of Applied Arts and Technology Act.Conestoga collects personal information from students to offer a comprehensive program of career-oriented, post-secondary education and training and for the following related purposes:making admission decisions and undertaking enrolmentproviding financial assistance and awardsproviding academic and ancillary servicesmaking advancement and graduation decisionsadministering the above activities providing a safe learning and working environmentConestoga considers student records to be confidential. It only discloses student personal information to third parties based on written consent, if required by law or as otherwise authorized by section 42 of the Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act. For example, section 42 of FIPPA permits the College to release personal information to aid a law enforcement investigation and to facilitate the auditing of government programs. The Ministry of Training, Colleges and Universities Act also requires the College to comply with Ministry reporting requirements that may entail the disclosure of student personal information along with statistical or aggregate information.For more information, or to request access to your personal information, you may contact our Access and Privacy Coordinator at the following address: Access and Privacy Coordinator Conestoga College Institute of Technology and Advanced Learning 299 Doon Valley Drive, Kitchener, Ontario, N2G 4M4 519-748-5220, ext. 2177 or
privacy@conestogac.on.ca. Further information about the Ministry’s collection of statistical and personal information can be obtained from the Government of Ontario or Ministry of Training, College and Universities website or by writing to:Director, Postsecondary Finance and Information Management Postsecondary Education Division 7th Floor, Mowat Block, 900 Bay St. Toronto, ON, M7A 1L2
